The Charles Shackford Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, 19---1979; Series I; 6.3' (12 boxes)
  - Music by Charles Shackford, I.A
    - [Fantasies, violoncello, piano, F] Fantasy in F for violoncello and piano. -- c1951., 1 score (30 p.), bound; 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 61)
      Holograph photocopy signed, with black and red pencil markings.
      Copyright in ink, caption.
      Revised version.
    - [Fantasies, violoncello, piano, F] Fantasy in F. -- 1951, (c1951)., 1 part; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G (Sketches)], 1 score (6, 11, 8 [i.e. 9] p.); 34 cm. (Box 3, Folder 63)
      Holograph in pencil and ink with ink and black and red pencil manuscript markings.
      With: Psalm 5, women's voices (Sketches) (1953), verso p. 1 (1st movement); and unidentified sketches, verso p. 6 (1st movement).
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G] Trio in G for oboe or flute, clarinet and bassoon. -- [1952, c1957]., 5 parts; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 64)
      Holograph signed, in ink with black and blue pencil and red ink manuscript markings.
      Includes extra parts (2nd movement) for oboe and clarinet.
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G] Trio in G for oboe or flute, clarinet and bassoon. -- 1952, c1977., 1 score (36 sheets); 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 65)
      Dedication: "For Ted Schultz".
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G] Trio in G, oboe, clarinet, bassoon. -- 1952, [c1977]., 3 parts; 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 66)
      Manuscript transparency in ink with pencil markings.
      "II Variations in Bb as well as A"--T.p., clarinet part.
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G] Trio in G. -- [1952, c1957]., 3 parts; 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 67)
      Manuscript transparencies in ink
      "Slightly inferior to other enveloped set"--Container.
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G] Trio in G, oboe, clarinet and bassoon. -- [1952, c1977]., 3 parts; 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 68)
      Manuscript transparencies.
      Oboe part for oboe or flute.
      "Slightly superior to other enveloped set"--Container.
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G] Trio in G for oboe or flute, clarinet and bassoon. -- 1952, [c1977]., 1 score (36 leaves); 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 69)
      Holograph (blueprint photocopy) with red ink manuscript markings.
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G] Trio in G for oboe or flute, clarinet and bassoon. -- 1952, [c1977]., 1 score (36 p.), bound; 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 70-71)
      Holograph (photocopy).
      2 copies.
      C. 1: Holograph title, signed, on cover. Ink and pencil markings.
      C. 2: Reproduction of corrected masters. Includes copyright.
    - [Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G] Trio in G, oboe, clarinet, bassoon. -- 1952, [c1977]., 4 parts 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 72)
      Manuscript (photocopy) with pencil manuscript markings.
      Includes additional clarinet part with 2nd movement written out for B-flat & A clarinets.
    - Give ear to my words, O Lord. -- 1953. (Box 3, Folder 72)
      See: Psalm 5, women's voices.
    - [Psalm 5, women's voices (Sketches)], 1 vocal score ([1] sheet); 35 cm. (Box 3, Folder 63)
      Sketches for verse 3t "My voice shalt thou hear".
      With: Trios, oboe, clarinet, bassoon, G (Sketches).
    - [Psalm 5, women's voices] Psalm V. -- c1953., 1 vocal score (10 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 73)
      For women's chorus (SSA).
      Holograph copyright, t.p.
      Dedication: "To the Wellesley College Choir 1952-1953 in remembrance of our year together".
      C. 2: without copyright. With publishers' addresses, verso, sheet 10.
    - [Psalm 5, women's voices] Verses from psalm 5: for three part unaccompanied female chorus. -- 1953, [c1953]., 1 vocal score (10 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 74)
      "Psalm 5 master sheets, September 1955"--Container.
      Dedication: "To the Wellesley College Choir 1952-1953".
      Differs slightly from earlier version.
    - [Psalm 5, women's voices] Verses from psalm 5: for three part unaccompanied female chorus. -- 1953, [c1953]., 1 vocal score (10 p.); 27 cm. (Box 3, Folder 74)
      Reproduction of 1955 masters.
    - [Have mercy upon me, O God] Psalm 51: verses 1 and 10. -- 1955., 1 vocal score (19 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 75)
      For chorus (SATB).
    - [Psalm 5, women's voices] Have mercy upon me, O God: Psalm 51. 1p 10. -- 1955., 1 vocal score (7 sheets); 36 cm. (Box 4, Folder 76)
      Cut and pasted.
      Dedication: "To St. Paul's, Chestnut Hill, Pa.".
      Commissioned by dedicatee.
    - [Psalm 5, women's voices] Have mercy upon me, O God: Psalm 51. 1p 10. -- 1955., 1 vocal score (7 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - [Have mercy upon me, O God; arr.] Psalm 51. -- [1955]., [3] p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 77)
      Rehearsal piano part without text.
    - Oh that men would praise the Lord (Box 4, Folder 77)
      See: Psalm 107.
    - Psalm 51 (Box 4, Folder 77)
      See: Have mercy upon me, O God.
    - [Psalm 107] Psalm 107: verses. -- 1955., 1 vocal score (10 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - [Psalm 107] Psalm 107. -- 1955., 1 vocal score (15 sheets); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 78)
      Title from caption.
      Dated: "September 1955"--Container.
      Dedication: "To Paul Hindemith".
    - [Psalm 107] Psalm 107. -- 1955., 1 vocal score (15 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - [Psalm 107] Psalm 107. -- 1955., 1 vocal score (15 p.); 23 cm. (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - [Sonatas, organ] Sonata for organ. -- c1956., [1], 18 sheets of music; 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 80)
      Dated: "March 1956"--Container.
      Dedication: "To H. Frank Bozyan".
      p. [1]: folksong (?) text in Low German (?).
    - [Sonatas, organ] Sonata for organ. -- c1956., 18 p. of music, bound; 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 81)
      Holograph (photocopy) signed, with pencil markings.
      Extra copy of text laid in.
    - [Te Deum. English (Sketches)], [31] p. of music; 31 cm. + [1] sheet of music; 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 82)
      Includes [11 sheet of unidentified sketches.
      2 cards with typescript text laid in.
    - [Te Deum. English] Te Deum in C. -- 1956., 1 vocal score (21 sheets); 34 cm. (Box 4, Folder 83)
      Holograph transparency in ink with typescript text.
      For chorus (SATB) and organ.
      Dated: "Wellesley, April 156".
    - [Te Deum. English] Te Deum in C. -- 1956., 1 vocal score (21 p.), bound; 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 84)
      Holograph (photocopy) with typescript text.
      "To the choir of St. Paul's, Chestnut Hill, Pa. on the occasion of the 100th anniversary of the church. For performance on Whitsunday, May 20, 1956"--T.p.
      Signed on cover in ink.
    - [Ode to learning (Sketches)]. -- 1959, [7] sheets of music; 28-32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - [Ode to learning], 1 vocal score (20 [i.e. 21] sheets); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 86)
      Holograph in pencil with ink markings.
    - [Ode to learning] An ode to learning. -- c1959., 1 vocal score (19 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 87)
      Holograph with typescript text (photocopy).
      Texts: New England's first fruits (1643) - The covenant of grace / words by Thomas Shepard (1651).
      For men's chorus (TTBB) and piano.
      Dated: "Wellesley Mass., Oct. '59".
      "For the glee club of the Hopkins Grammar School, New Haven on the occasion of the 300th anniversary of the school. For performance on May 13, 1960."--Caption.
    - [Nunc dimittises, women's voices. English] Nunc dimittis. -- 1964., 1 vocal score ([1] sheet); 36 cm. (Box 4, Folder 88)
      Holograph with typescript caption and text (photocopy).
      For chorus (SSAA).
    - Lord is my shepherd (Sketches). -- 1966 (Box 4, Folder 88)
      See: Sketchbooks (ca. 1967).
    - [Lord is my shepherd] The Lord is my shepherd: psalm 23: mixed chorus (SATB). -- c1966., 1 vocal score (8 sheets); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 89)
      Holograph transparency signed, in ink with typescript caption, text, and copyright.
    - [Lord is my shepherd] The Lord is my shepherd: psalm 23: mixed chorus (SATB). -- c1966., 1 vocal score (8 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - [Lord is my shepherd; arr.] The Lord is my shepherd: psalm 23: female chorus (SSAA). -- c1966., 1 vocal score (8 sheets); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - [Lord is my shepherd; arr.] The Lord is my shepherd: psalm 23: female chorus (SSAA). -- c1966., 1 vocal score [2] leaves); 20-22 cm. (Box 4, Folder 90)
      p. 9, 6.
      4 copies.
    - [Lord is my shepherd; arr.] The Lord is my shepherd: psalm 23: female chorus (SSAA). -- c1966., 1 vocal score (8 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 90)
      1 copy: "Sample"--Note laid in.
    - [Lord is my shepherd; arr.] The Lord is my shepherd: psalm 23: female chorus (SSAA). -- c1966., 1 vocal score (8 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Psalm 23 (Box 4, Folder 90)
      See: Lord is my shepherd.
    - [Bless the Lord, O my soul], 1 score (8 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 91)
      For unison chorus, trumpet, horn, 2 trombones, and tuba.
    - [Bless the Lord, O my soul] "Bless the Lord, O my soul" (psalm 104): For unison chorus and brass: score. -- c1967., 1 score [i], 8 p.); 34 cm. (Box 4, Folder 91)
      Holograph signed, in pencil with red pencil markings.
      Verses 1, 4, 23, 31.
      Dedication: "To the class of 1967, Connecticut College"--p. [i].
    - [Bless the Lord, O my soul] "Bless the Lord, O my soul": For unison chorus and brass. -- c1967., 5 parts; 34 cm. (Box 4, Folder 92)
      Brass parts.
    - [Bless the Lord, O my soul] "Bless the Lord, O my soul": (psalm 104): for unison chorus and brass: score. -- c1967., 1 score ([ii], 8 sheets); 38-35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 93)
      Ink copyright, t.p.
      Without p. [i].
      C. 1: Holograph copyright in ink, t.p. Without p. [i].
      C. 2: With p. [i].
    - [Bless the Lord, O my soul] "Bless the Lord, O my soul": psalm 104: for unison chorus and brass. -- c1967., 5 parts; 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 94)
      Holograph (photocopy) signed, in ink with pencil markings.
      Set of brass parts.
    - [Bless the Lord, O my soul. Vocal score] Bless the Lord, O my soul. -- c1967., 1 vocal score (9 sheets); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 95)
      For unison chorus and organ.
    - [Bless the Lord, O my soul. Vocal score] "Bless the Lord, O my soul" (psalm 104): for unison chorus & brass: organ arrangement. -- c1967., 1 vocal score (9 p.); 26 cm. (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Psalm 104 (Box 4, Folder 95)
      See: Bless the Lord, O my soul.
    - [Sketchbooks (ca. 1967)], [168] sheets of music; 27-28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 96-98)
      Holograph in pencil with typescript texts and manuscript in pencil.
      Miscellaneous sketches including O sing unto the Lord, Lord is my shepherd, and other psalms. Also lecture notes (?) and exercises by students.
      Originally in loose leaf binder.
    - [Toccata, brasses] Toccata. -- c1967., 1 score (7 [i.e. 8] p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 99)
      6 parts reduced to 4 staffs.
      For 2 trumpets, horn, 2 trombones, and tuba.
    - [Toccata, brasses] Toccata for six brass instruments: score. -- c1967., 1 score (9 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 99)
      Dated: "Waterford, Conn. Oct. 1967.".
    - [Toccata, brasses] Toccata for six brass instruments. -- 1967, [c1967]., 6 parts; 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - [Toccata, brasses] Toccata. -- c1967., 1 score (8 sheets); 38 cm. (Box 4, Folder 101)
      Reproduction of 4 staff score.
    - [Toccata, brasses] Toccata. 1967, [c1967]., 1 score ([3] sheets); 35-38 cm. (Box 4, Folder 101)
      Reproduction of p. 1, 2 of full score.
      Includes transparency ([1] sheet) with ink copyright.
    - O sing unto the Lord (Sketches). -- 1968. (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - [O sing unto the Lord] O sing unto the Lord (SATB): psalm 96: 1, 6, 9, 11-13. -- c1968., 1 vocal score (9 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 5, Folder 102)
      Holograph in pencil with typescript t.p., caption, and copyright
      For chorus.
    - [O sing unto the Lord] O sing unto the Lord (SATB): psalm 96: 1, 6, 9, 11-13. -- c1968., 1 vocal score (9 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - [O sing unto the Lord, arr.] O sing unto the Lord: psalm 96: 1, 6, 9, 11-13. -- c1968., 1 vocal score (9 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 5, Folder 103)
      Holograph in pencil with typescript caption, and copyright.
      For women's chorus (SSAA).
    - [O sing unto the Lord; arr.] O sing unto the Lord: female chorus (SSAA): psalm 96: 1, 6, 9, 11-13. -- c1968., 1 vocal score (9 p.); 27 cm. (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Psalm 96 (Box 5, Folder 103)
      See: O sing unto the Lord.
    - [Fantasy on Vysehrad (Sketches)], [9] sheets of music; 28 cm. (Box 5, Folder 104)
      Contains [8] sheets of unidentified sketches.
    - [Fantasy on Vysehrad (Sketches)] Fantasy for two pianos and orchestra. -- [1969, c1975]., 1 short score (50 p.); 35 cm. (Box 5, Folder 104)
      [3] sheets of music; 34 cm.
      First 83 measures of part for solo pianos.
      [3] leaves, [2] p. of music; 34 cm.
      Holograph in ink with pencil markings.
      Excerpts of wind parts.
    - [Fantasy on Vysehrad] Fantasy on "Vysehrad" for two pianos and orchestra: score. -- 1969. 1975., 1 score (152 [i.e. 143] p.); 34 cm. (Box 5, Folder 105)
      Holograph t.p. in pencil laid in.
      "Waterford, Connecticut. 2 May (3:15 a.m.) 1969. Begun July 1968. Laus Deo, finita est"--At end.
      "Commissioned by Connecticut College for the dedication of the Charles A. Dana Concert Hall, May 10, 1969."--Typescript and printed slips of paper laid in.
      2 slips of paper with copyright laid in.
    - [Fantasy on Vysehrad] Fantasy on Vysehrad for two pianos and orchestra: piano parts. -- 1969, [c1975]., 1 score (47 p.); 35 cm. (Box 5, Folder 106)
      Part for solo pianos.
      Includes master t.p.
    - [Fantasy on Vysehrad] Fantasy on "Vysehrad" for two pianos and orchestra score. -- 1969, [c1975]., 1 score (143 p.), bound; 35 cm. (Box 5, Folder 107-108)
      Holograph (photocopy) signed, with red ink markings.
      2 copies, with slight differences in corrections.
      Does not include reproductions of copyright and commission information.
    - [Fantasy on Vysehrad] Fantasy on "Vysehrad" for two pianos and orchestra score. -- 1969, [c1975]., 1 score (143 p.), bound; 36 cm. (Box 5, Folder 109)
      "Correction Copy"--Cover.
      With reproductions of dedication and copyright.
    - [Fantasy on Vysehrad] Fantasy on "Vysehrad": piano parts. -- 1969, [c1975]., 1 score (47 p.), bound; 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 110)
      Holograph title on cover.
    - [Fantasy on Vysehrad] Fantasy on "Vysehrad" for two pianos and orchestra. -- [1969, c1975]., 19 parts; 34 cm. (Box 6, Folder 111-113)
      Manuscript (photocopy) with holograph inserts and red ink holograph and pencil manuscript markings.
      Includes 2 copies of 1st violin part.
    - [Orpheus (Sketches)] Setting of Orpheus. -- Nov. 1969., p. 5-115 [i.e. 1, 63 sheets] of music; 14-28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 114)
      "Orpheus" for soprano, oboe and harp. Poem by William Meredith"--Enclosure with letter to Charles A. Dana. See: III.A CORRESPONDENCE. From CBS.
      Includes [2] sheets of holograph scenario and some unidentified sketches (sheets [i, 11]).
      Photocopy of text laid in.
    - Vysehrad (Box 6, Folder 114)
      See: Fantasy on Vysehrad.
    - Behold how good and pleasant it is (Sketches). -- 1970. (Box 6, Folder 114)
      See: Sketchbooks (ca. 1970).
    - [Behold how good and pleasant it is] Behold how good and pleasant it is (psalm 133): SSAA. -- c1970., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 115)
      For women's chorus.
      Dated: "New London, 27 Jan, '70".
    - [Behold how good and pleasant it is] Behold how good and pleasant it is: psalm 133. -- 1970, [c1970]., 1 vocal score (5 sheets); 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - [Behold how good and pleasant it is] Behold how good and pleasant it is (psalm 133): SSAA. -- c1970., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 27 cm. (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Psalm 133 (Box 6, Folder 115)
      See: Behold how good and pleasant it is.
    - [Selections (Sketches)], [2] sheets, [2] leaves, [9] p. of music; 34 cm. (Box 6, Folder 116)
      Miscellaneous sketches.
      From ca. 1970 (?).
    - [Sketchbooks (ca. 1970)], [85] sheets of music; 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 117-118)
      Miscellaneous sketches including Behold how good and pleasant it is and other psalms
    - [Suites, piano] Suite for piano. -- 1970, c1977., 15 sheets of music; 36 cm. (Box 6, Folder 119)
      Holograph transparency signed, in pencil.
      Dedication: "To Jane".
      Mostly reworking of Piano pieces from Selections (19--).
    - [Suites, piano] Suite for piano. -- 1970, c1977., 15 p. of music; 36 cm. (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - [Blessed is the man] Blessed is the man: psalm I: female chorus (SSAA). -- c1971., 1 vocal score (15 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 121)
      Dated: "New London, Sept. 1971".
    - [Blessed is the man] Blessed is the man: psalm I: female chorus (SSAA). -- c1971., 1 vocal score (15 sheets), bound; 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 122)
      Typescript letter of rejection from G. Schirmer laid in.
    - [Blessed is the man] Blessed is the man: psalm 1: female chorus (SSAA). -- c1971., 1 vocal score (15 p.); 27 cm. (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - [I will lift up mine eyes] I will lift up mine eyes: psalm 121. -- c1971., 1 vocal score (14 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 123)
      Dated: "New London, April 14, 1971".
    - [I will lift up mine eyes] I will lift up mine eyes: psalm 121. -- c1971., 1 vocal score (14 leaves), bound; 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - [Nunc dimittises, mixed voices. English] Nune dimittis: St. Luke II: 29-32. -- c1971., 1 vocal score (4 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - [Nunc dimittises, mixed voices. English] Nunc dimittis: St. Luke II: 29-32. -- 1971, [c1971]., 1 vocal score (4 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Psalm 1 (Box 6, Folder 125)
      See: Blessed is the man.
    - Psalm 121 (Box 6, Folder 125)
      See: I will lift up mine eyes.
    - [I was glad when they said unto me (Sketches)], [10] sheets of music; 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 126)
      With: Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat (Sketches), recto, sheet [1].
    - [I was glad when they said unto me] I was glad when they said unto me: psalm 122: verses 1, 2, 7, 9. -- c1972., 1 vocal score (14 sheets); 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 126)
      Dated: "New London, November 1972".
    - [I was glad when they said unto me] I was glad when they said unto me: psalm 122: verses 1, 2, 7, 9. -- 1972 [c1972]., 1 vocal score (14 sheets): 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - [I was glad when they said unto me] I was glad when they said unto me: psalm 122: verses 1, 2, 7, 9. -- 1972 [c1972]., 1 vocal score (14 sheets): 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 126)
      Copy of masters before full tempo indication and dynamics had been added.
    - [I was glad when they said unto me] I was glad when they said unto me: female chorus (SSAA). -- c1972., 1 vocal score (14 p.); 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 126)
      Title from t.p.
      Dedication: "For Paul L. Althouse".
    - Psalm 122 (Box 6, Folder 126)
      See: I was glad when they said unto me.
    - [Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat, (Sketches)], [21, 1, 3] sheets, [20] p. of music; 28-34 cm. (Box 7, Folder 127)
      Identification difficult. Roger Blanc's identification of last 10 sheets as for this work doubtful.
    - [Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat, (Sketches)], [1] sheet of music; 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 126)
      With: I was glad when they said unto me (Sketches) (1972).
    - [Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat] Quintet for clarinet in Bb, horn in F, violin, viola and violoncello. -- 1973, [c1975]., 1 score (59 p.); 35 cm. (Box 7, Folder 128)
      Dated: "New London, Conn. April 1, 1973".
      Duration, 1st movement: 10:26.
    - [Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat] Quintet. -- 1973, [c1975]., 5 parts; 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 129)
      Manuscript transparency in ink.
    - [Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat] Quintet in Eb for clarinet, French horn, violin, viola, violoncello. -- 1973, c1975., 1 score (58 [i.e. i, 29 sheets]); 35 cm. (Box 7, Folder 130)
      Odd numbered sheets missing.
      Cut and pasted t.p.
      "In memory of my father and my mother William Moore Shackford, Olive Schley Shackford"--Sheet [i].
    - [Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat] Quintet. -- 1973, [c1975]., 5 parts; 36 cm. (Box 7, Folder 131)
      Manuscript (blueprint photocopy) with red pencil manuscript corrections.
    - [Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat] Quintet in Eb for clarinet, French horn, violin, viola, and violoncello. -- 1973, c1975. (Box 7, Folder 132-133)
      C. 1: "Poor"--Cover.
      Pencil corrections to violoncello part (p. 26, c. 1).
    - [Quintets, clarinet, horn, violin, viola, violoncello, E-flat] Quintet. -- 1973, [c1975]., 5 parts; 32-33 cm. (Box 7, Folder 134-136)
      Manuscript (photocopy) with black and red ink and black and red pencil holograph and manuscript markings.
      3 copies.
      C. 2: "Correction set".
      C. 3: corrected, lacking clarinet part.
    - [Overture concertante (Sketches)], [74] sheets of music; 27 x 30 cm. (Box 7, Folder 137)
      Holograph in pencil with red ink markings.
      "Band Piece"--Container.
    - [Overture concertante (Sketches)], 16 (i.e. 15] sheets of music; 28 cm. (Box 7, Folder 138)
      "Sketch for Overture Concertante"--Container.
      See also: D. By Charles Shackford, Oversize Materials.
    - [Overture concertante], 1 part; 22 x 28 cm. (Box 7, Folder 139)
      Manuscript (photocopy) with red ink markings.
      Measures 210-285 of 1st cornet part.
    - [Overture concertante] Overture Concertante. -- c1974., 30 parts; 33 cm. (Box 7, Folder 140-142, Box 8)
      Manuscript (photocopy) with red ink holograph and pencil manuscript markings.
    - [Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G (Sketches)], [11, 4], 8, [11] sheets of music; 27 cm. (Box 8, Folder 143-144)
      Holograph in pencil and red ink.
    - [Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G] Quintet in G for oboe, trumpet, alto saxophone, violoncello and bass. -- 1974., 1 score (30 p.); 35 cm. (Box 8, Folder 145)
      Holograph in pencil with ink dedication.
      1st movement dated: "New London, Connecticut, March 27, 1974".
      2nd movement dated: "New London, Conn. 11 April 1974".
      Dedication: "For Chris Vadala".
      2nd movement t.p., found separately, laid in.
    - [Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G] Quintet. -- 1974., 5 parts; 16-33 cm. (Box 8, Folder 146-147)
    - [Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G] Quintet in G for oboe, trumpet, alto saxophone, violoncello and bass. -- 1974. (Box 8, Folder 148)
      Holograph (photocopy on transparency) signed.
      T.p. (holograph signed, in ink) laid in.
    - [Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G] Quintet in G for oboe, trumpet, alto saxophone, violoncello and bass. -- 1974., 1 score (30 p.), bound; 35 cm. (Box 8, Folder 149)
      Holograph (photocopy) signed, with manuscript pencil markings.
    - [Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G] Quintet. -- 1974., 5 parts; 33 cm. (Box 8, Folder 150-151)
    - [Quintets, oboe, trumpet, saxophone, violoncello, double bass, G], [33] sheets of music; 22 x 28 cm. (Box 8, Folder 152)
      Holograph (photocopy) signed, with black and blue pencil manuscript markings.
      Partial p. of score reproduced on each sheet.
    - [Serenades, harpsichord, flute, clarinet, D] Serenade in D. -- [1975, c1976]., 1 score (14, 5, 15 p.); 33 cm. (Box 8, Folder 153)
      Sketches for 1st movement (?) on t.p.